https://www.australiantimes.co.uk/terms-and-conditions/

1.  Who we are
We are AustralianTimes.co.uk, an online news publication published by Blue Sky Publications.
We are registered in the United Kingdom.
United Kingdom – Blue Sky Publications Ltd – registration number 046836392. You can find us at Riverbank House, 1 Putney Bridge Approach, London, SW6 4TJ
2.  Content on this website
Most of the content on this website is ours and subject to our copyright, but some of the content is owned by others. For instance where we link to other websites.
You may:
use and enjoy the content for your own personal information purposes; andshare our posts on social media.
If you want to use the content for any other purpose, please ask our permission first. You can contact us at info@australiantimes.co.uk.
3.  Rules of use
Do comply with all applicable laws when using our website.Don’t use any element of our website, including our name, logo, trademark and design, without out written consent.Don’t use any automated means (like spiders or crawlers or interface that we have not authorised) to access the website, extract data or otherwise interfere with or modify content, functionality or rendering.Don’t access or tamper with non-public areas of the website, our computer systems, or any of our suppliers’ systems.Don’t avoid, deactivate, reverse engineer or damage any security measures that protect our website.Don’t forge headers or manipulate identifiers to disguise the origin of content.Don’t upload content or any file to our website.Don’t create new links for our content.Don’t send us spam, ads or malicious communication.Don’t reproduce, copy, sell, trade, resell or exploit any part of the website for commercial reasons.
4.  Opinions
The opinions of advertisers, writers, commenters and contributors are theirs and do not necessarily reflect the opinion of australiantimes.co.uk, Blue Sky Publications or any of our affiliates.
5.  Your personal information
We will keep your personal information confidential. Read our privacy notice to see how we collect and use personal information.
6.  Third-party websites
Sometimes we link to third-party websites that are not ours or under our control. We cannot accept responsibility for the quality, content, nature, or reliability of third-party websites.
PRIVACY NOTICE
1.  What this notice is about
During  our interactions, you share personal information with australiantimes.co.uk, a division of Blue Sky Publications (Pty) Ltd.
This notice tells you what to expect when we collect and use
your information. We may need to update it occasionally, but we will inform you
when we do. You should read this notice along with the terms of use.
If you have any questions, please contact us at info@australiantimes.co.uk
2.  We
collect your information when you interact with us
2.1.
When you contact us, we collect information from
your message
When you contact us by social media, email, telephone, or
online chat with a query, complaint, or request, we collect the information
included in your message. We use the information we collect to reply to,
investigate, and resolve your query, complaint, or request.
Legal basis for processing
Data protection
legislation allows us to process personal information when it is in our interest
and we have chosen the least invasive way to process the information. It is in
both our interest to reply to, investigate, and resolve your queries,
complaints, and requests.
2.2.
When you send us your CV and writing examples
If you are
interested in writing for us, you may send us your CV and an example of your
writing. We will use this information to consider you as a volunteer writer.
Legal basis for processing
Data protection
legislation allows us to process personal information when it is necessary to
take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract, or for the
performance of a contract with you.
2.3.
When you subscribe to our newsletter
We have a weekly newsletter  that is delivered by email.
We’ll ask you whether you want to receive the newsletter, and
if you agree it is important that you know you can unsubscribe at any time by
following the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email or contacting us.
Legal basis for processing
Data protection
legislation allows us to process personal information when you have given us
your consent for direct marketing.
2.4.  When you take part in a survey
You may choose to complete your name and contact details
when you take part in one of our surveys, although you always have the option
to take part anonymously. We may use this information to give you feedback
about the survey.
Legal basis for processing
Data protection
legislation allows us to process personal information when it is necessary for
the performance of a contract with you.
2.5.  When you take part in a competition
We will use your information to administer the competition
and to communicate with you about the competition.
Legal basis for processing
Data protection legislation
allows us to process personal information when it is necessary for the
performance of a contract with you.
3.  We
share your information with others we trust
We use suppliers and service providers who we trust to
assist us in providing our services to you. They have agreed to keep your
information secure and confidential, and to only use it for the purposes for
which we have shared it with them.
We share your
information with service providers when they help us:
to
store informationto
manage our social media interactionsto
deliver our newsletterto
help monitor the effectiveness of our promotions and advertisingto
manage our business, for instance accountants and professional advisorswith
IT servicesto
maintain our website
Sometimes we will be required by law to share your
information. For instance, we may be required to share your information with the
authorities or with regulatory bodies.
We will not share your information with third parties for the purposes of direct marketing.
4.  We
send your information to other countries
Some of the service providers that we use may be located in other countries. For instance, our cloud storage service. These countries may not have the same levels of protection of personal information as the United Kingdom. If this is the case, we require that they undertake to protect the personal information of our users to the same level that we do.
We provide for appropriate safeguards by means of contracts
between us and our foreign service providers.
5.  We
don’t keep your information longer than we need to
We will not retain your information for longer than we need
to, unless we are legally required to.
6.  We
have taken reasonable steps to minimise the impact of a breach
We have implemented reasonable security measures based on
the sensitivity of the information we hold. These measures are in place to
protect the information from being disclosed, from loss, misuse, and
unauthorised access, and from being altered, or destroyed.
If something should happen, we have taken steps to minimise
the threat to your privacy. We will let you know of any breaches that affect
your personal information and we will inform you how you can help minimise the
impact.
7.  You
have the right to be informed about the personal information we have, and what
we do with it
You have the right to
ask
us what we know about you;ask
what information was sent to our suppliers, service providers, or any other
third party; ask
us to update or correct any out-of-date or incorrect personal information we
hold about you;ask
us to delete the personal information we hold about you;unsubscribe
from any direct marketing communications we may send you; and object
to the processing of our personal information.
You can request access to the information we hold about you or correct your personal information by contacting our deputy information officer by emailing info@australiantimes.co.uk.
It can take us up to 21 days to respond to your request,
because there are procedures that we need to follow. In certain cases, we may
require proof of your identity.
8.  Your rights in terms of the GDPR
If you are in the European Union, you have these rights in
terms of the GDPR:
The right to be informed about the collection and use of your personal information.The right to access your personal information. You may make such a request from us by contacting info@australiantimes.co.uk.  We may take one month to respond to your request and may charge a fee in some circumstances. We will let you know if this is the case. You have a right to have inaccurate personal information corrected or completed if it is incomplete. You may make such a request from us by contacting info@australiantimes.co.uk.  We may take one month to respond to your request and may refuse in certain circumstances.You have the right to have your personal information erased, also known as the ‘right to be forgotten’. You may make such a request from us by contacting info@australiantimes.co.uk.  We may take one month to respond to your request and may refuse in certain circumstances.You have the right to request that we restrict or suppress your personal information. You may make such a request from us by contacting info@australiantimes.co.uk. We may take one month to respond to your request and may refuse in certain circumstances.You have the right to reuse your personal information for your own purposes across different services, also known as the right to data portability. You have the right to object to us processing your personal information in certain circumstances. You may make your objection by contacting info@australiantimes.co.uk.  We may take one month to respond to your request. There are legitimate reasons why we may refuse your objection, which depend on why we are processing your personal information.You have the right to complain to a supervisory authority in the Member State where you live or work, or where the infringement took place.
COOKIE NOTICE
1.  What this notice is about
Our website, like many others, stores information on and
retrieves information from your browser using cookies. Cookies are files
containing small amounts of data (usually text) that a website generates and
saves through your web browser. Cookies can be used to improve how efficiently a
website functions, remember certain information about its users, or even to
keep a website operational. It is not personally identifiable to you, but
it can be used to give you a more personalised web experience. Some cookies are
only kept per session, and some are saved for persistent use.
You should read this notice along with our privacy notice.
This table explains the cookies
we use and why:
Cookie
Name
Purpose
Universal Analytics (Google)
These cookies collect information about your use of our website including
your IP address and may be transmitted to Google and stored on their servers.
These cookies are used to compile reports and to help us improve our website.
The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of
visitors to the website, from where visitors have come to the website, and
the pages they visited.
For more information visit http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/
Advertising (Google)
Doubleclick
cookie – id
This is a
tracking cookie used by Google to improve your online experience, including
the display of more relevant advertisements.
YouTube is used by the website to store and show video content. These
cookies are set by YouTube to track usage of its services. The YouTube
Cookies are only installed when you press play.
For more information visit http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/
We collect the information from your device e.g. operating system and
browser, mobile tracking information, IP address, the website you visited
prior to ours, your language, country, interactions with our website and the
behaviour of our platform to ensure the website is displayed in the best
format possible and to serve contextualised advertisements and personalised
recommendations to you.
2.  You
can change your cookie settings
Because we respect your right to privacy, you can choose to
change your privacy preferences to prevent non-essential cookies being
set.
To find out more about cookies, including how to see what
cookies have been set visit www.aboutcookies.org.
To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all
websites visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
If you have any questions, please contact us at info@australiantimes.co.uk.
Copyright © Blue Sky Publications Ltd. All Rights Reserved. australiantimes.co.uk is
a division of Blue Sky Publications Ltd.
Reproduction without permission prohibited.
Copyright © Blue Sky Publications Ltd. All Rights Reserved. australiantimes.co.uk is
a division of Blue Sky Publications Ltd.
Reproduction without permission prohibited.
